[{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":38434,"timeElapsed":156383},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980489550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":21420,"timeElapsed":177807},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":18644,"timeElapsed":196456},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980532129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":23926,"timeElapsed":220386},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":12949,"timeElapsed":233339},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":40197,"timeElapsed":273538},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":34124,"timeElapsed":307667},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":9574,"timeElapsed":317245},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980636710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7718,"timeElapsed":324967},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":40191,"timeElapsed":369054},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":22796,"timeElapsed":391853},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980719277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":15677,"timeElapsed":407534},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":11633,"timeElapsed":419171},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980741082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":10164,"timeElapsed":429339},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":10884,"timeElapsed":440227},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":13654,"timeElapsed":453883},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8895,"timeElapsed":462781},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":10718,"timeElapsed":473504},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980810426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":20437,"timeElapsed":498683},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":10988,"timeElapsed":509674},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":13045,"timeElapsed":522722},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":9516,"timeElapsed":532242},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":26955,"timeElapsed":559201},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":8899,"timeElapsed":568103},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":8915,"timeElapsed":577022},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980893461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4693,"timeElapsed":581718},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980898471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5007,"timeElapsed":586728},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980923524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":23109,"timeElapsed":611781},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980928428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4901,"timeElapsed":616685},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980932509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4077,"timeElapsed":620766},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980937595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":5083,"timeElapsed":625852},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980942118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4520,"timeElapsed":630375},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980946475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4355,"timeElapsed":634732},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980951691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5212,"timeElapsed":639948},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980956195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4501,"timeElapsed":644452},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980960758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4561,"timeElapsed":649015},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":15874,"timeElapsed":666688},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980985053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6618,"timeElapsed":673310},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980989818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4762,"timeElapsed":678075},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980999767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9946,"timeElapsed":688024},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981004712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4942,"timeElapsed":692969},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981009133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4417,"timeElapsed":697390},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981014272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5135,"timeElapsed":702529},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981019987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5712,"timeElapsed":708244},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981024116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4126,"timeElapsed":712373},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981040970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":14764,"timeElapsed":729227},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981048034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7060,"timeElapsed":736291},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981054467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6430,"timeElapsed":742724},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981060514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6044,"timeElapsed":748771},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981074377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":13861,"timeElapsed":762634},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981089021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":14641,"timeElapsed":777278},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981104125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":15102,"timeElapsed":792382},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981109260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5131,"timeElapsed":797517},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981114943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5679,"timeElapsed":803199},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981129784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":13001,"timeElapsed":818041},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981135221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5434,"timeElapsed":823478},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981139675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4450,"timeElapsed":827932},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981144357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4679,"timeElapsed":832614},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981152044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7684,"timeElapsed":840301},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981159144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7097,"timeElapsed":847401},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981164474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5326,"timeElapsed":852731},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981169396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4919,"timeElapsed":857653},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981174552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5153,"timeElapsed":862809},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981184869,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10313,"timeElapsed":873125},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981202299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":15247,"timeElapsed":890556},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981208316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6014,"timeElapsed":896573},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981213924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5605,"timeElapsed":902181},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981220125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":6197,"timeElapsed":908382},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981225465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":5337,"timeElapsed":913722},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981231528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":6060,"timeElapsed":919785},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981238054,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6523,"timeElapsed":926311},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981244162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":6106,"timeElapsed":932419},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981249597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5431,"timeElapsed":937853},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981254076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4476,"timeElapsed":942332},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981268099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":11585,"timeElapsed":956356},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981272849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4747,"timeElapsed":961106},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981278086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5233,"timeElapsed":966342},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981282037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3948,"timeElapsed":970294},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981285972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3931,"timeElapsed":974228},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981290045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4070,"timeElapsed":978302},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981294807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4759,"timeElapsed":983064},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981300525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":5715,"timeElapsed":988782},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981306549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":6022,"timeElapsed":994806},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981317448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8788,"timeElapsed":1005705},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981322390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4938,"timeElapsed":1010647},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981328722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":6329,"timeElapsed":1016979},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981333706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4982,"timeElapsed":1021963},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981338641,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4931,"timeElapsed":1026898},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981343875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5232,"timeElapsed":1032132},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981350375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6497,"timeElapsed":1038632},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981355211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4833,"timeElapsed":1043467},{"subjectID":"6nebk4ezt8","prolificID":"672f38145bf80a772f4ac20a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2c1bc79193f7a35208a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981360612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":5400,"timeElapsed":1048869}]